secumd.org 2010-06-16

# SECU Credit Union - Online Loans, Free Checking, Online Banking

****

**SECU Member's Right to Privacy and Confidentiality**

****

** ** SECU is owned by its members and run by a Board of Directors you elect. You can be confident that your financial privacy is a top priority of this Credit Union. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your personal financial information. If you have any questions, please contact a Member Services Representative at SECU, 971 Corporate Blvd., Linthicum, MD 21090-2337, 4l0-487-7328.

**SECU Credit Union never requests sensitive account information through unsolicited e-mail to members.**

If you receive an **unsolicited** e-mail claiming to be from SECU or any other group requesting that you provide your account numbers, Social Security number, personal identification numbers (PINs), passwords, or other confidential information, do not divulge any information, do not click on any links, and report the suspected fraudulent e-mail to the Internet Fraud Complaint Center at [www.ic3.gov/](http://www.ic3.gov/).

At SECU, we respect your right to privacy and confidentiality. Safeguarding your assets and accounts \- and all financial and personal information related to those accounts \- is our responsibility. Our policies and procedures are developed and implemented with that objective in mind. We have selected our computer system and software based on their ability to control access to your information.

**Categories of Information that SECU Collects About You**

Your relationship is important to us and we are committed to providing you with the best products and services possible. To do that, we collect nonpublic personal information from a variety of sources to keep you informed about the many financial services, products, and benefits available to you as a SECU member. We also collect information to comply with laws and regulations and to protect you against fraud. For example, we collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * Information we received from you on membership and loan applications and other forms; 
  * Information about your transactions with us or others; 
  * Information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency; 
  * Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on an application or other forms, such as from your current or past employers or from other institutions where you conduct financial transactions; 
  * Web site information. 

**Categories of Information that SECU Discloses About You**

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our members or former members to anyone, except as permitted, authorized, or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to follow your instructions as you authorize, to conduct the operations of the Credit Union, or to protect the security of our financial records. To protect our members' privacy, we only work with companies that agree to maintain strong confidentiality protections and limit the use of information we provide. We do not permit these companies to sell to other third parties the information we provide.

**Opting Out of Promotional Mailings**

You can choose not to receive marketing offers from us via direct mail or e-mail. Simply call our Contact Center at 410-487-7328 or 800-879-7328 (outside of Baltimore), or e-mail ask.secumd.com and opt out of promotional mailings. This does not affect statement mailings. 

**How SECU Protects Your Information**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and leading industry practices to safeguard your nonpublic personal information.

**E-mail Communication Between Members and SECU**

** ** Do not include account numbers, social security numbers, personal identification numbers (PINs), passwords, or other confidential information in your e-mail messages to SECU Credit Union. E-mail transmissions are not encrypted.

**Third-Party Links**

Links are available on SECU Credit Union's website that allow convenient access to other sites that may be of interest. Clicking on a link may take you out of SECU's website to an alternative website not operated by SECU Credit Union. SECU is not responsible for content on third-party websites and does not represent either the third-party websites or the member if he or she enters into a transaction. While we hope these organizations join us in respecting your privacy, SECU Credit Union is not responsible for the content, products, services, or privacy practices of these third-party websites. Linked sites may have privacy policies that are different from SECU Credit Union. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.

**SECU's Right to Amend**

SECU reserves the right to amend this disclosure at any time without prior notice. This disclosure amends existing agreements that the Credit Union has with you.
